A Guide to the Virginia Quartermaster's Department Records, 1861-1864
Library of Virginia
- Smoot, L. R.
  - Abstract N, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Accounts, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-32, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-45, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers (Fractional), Nos. 1-17, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Abstract C - Vouchers, Nos. 1-5, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Abstract C - Vouchers (Fractional), 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-8, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-3, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers (Fractional), 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-30, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers (Fractional), 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Abstract N, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Abstract of Salt Accounts - Vouchers, Nos. 1-80, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Abstract of Salt Accounts - Vouchers, Nos. 81-97, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Accounts, 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Accounts, 1863, 3rd Quarter (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Accounts, 1864 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Snead, G.T.
  - Abstract A, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-37, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Abstract A - Commissary Dept. - Vouchers, Nos. 1-12, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-52, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-5, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Abstract G, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Abstract L, 1862, 4th Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-9, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Abstract A, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Abstracts and vouchers, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-23, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Abstract A - Commissary Dept. - Vouchers, Nos. 1-5, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-63, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-28, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-17, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-6, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-4, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-7, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Abstract L, 1863, 1st Quarter (See Oversize) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-17, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-8, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Abstract N, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Venable, C.W.
  - Accounts, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-16, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Abstract A - Commissary Dept. - Vouchers, Nos. 1-19, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Abstract E-N, 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Accounts, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-41, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-11, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Abstract E, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Abstract M, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Accounts, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Abstract A - Vouchers, Nos. 1-40, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Abstract A - Commissary Dept. - Vouchers, Nos. 1-27, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 1-70, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Abstract B - Vouchers, Nos. 71-117, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Abstract B - Contingencies - Vouchers, Nos. 1-9, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Abstract Bb - Vouchers, Nos. 1-4, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Abstract E - Vouchers, Nos. 1-12, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Abstract F - Vouchers, Nos. 1-16, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Abstract G - Vouchers, Nos. 1-48, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Abstract K - Vouchers, Nos. 1-27, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Abstract L - Vouchers, Nos. 1-7, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Abstract M - Vouchers, Nos. 1-17, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Abstract N, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Oversize Records
  - Caruthers, W.H., 1861 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Echols, R.J., 1861 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Goodloe, J.B. - Abstracts A-B, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Goodloe, J.B. - Abstracts E-N, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, J.K. - Abstracts A-Bb, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Johnson, J.K. - Abstracts D-N, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Officers Appointed, 1861 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Richmond and Danville Railroad Co., 1862 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Smoot, L.R., 1861, 3rd Quarter (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Smoot, L.R., 1861, 4th Quarter (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Smoot, L.R., 1862, 1st Quarter (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Smoot, L.R. - Abstract B, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Smoot, L.R., 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ficklin, B.F., 1861 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Goodloe, J.B., 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Goodloe, J.B., 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Goodloe, J.B., 1863, 2nd Quarter (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Goodloe, J.B., 1863, 3rd Quarter (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Harman, J.A., 1861, 2nd Quarter (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lechenet, L., 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Lechenet, L., 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous Accounts, 1862 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Rocke, F.G., 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Rocke, F.G., 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Smoot, L.R., 1862, 2nd Quarter (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Smoot, L.R., 1862, 3rd Quarter (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Smoot, L.R. - Abstract A, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Smoot, L.R. - Abstracts C-M, 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Smoot, L.R. - Abstracts A-M, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Smoot, L.R., 1863, 2nd and 3rd Quarter, and 1864 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Snead, G.T., 1862, 4th Quarter (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Snead, G.T., 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Venable, C.W., 1862, 3rd and 4th Quarters (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Venable, C.W., 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Venable, C.W. - Abstracts A-N, 1863, 1st Quarter (Box 20, Folder 11)